Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Photographs PHOTOS 019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: New York Teacher Photograph Files, 1951-1987.
  - Subseries I:B: New York State United Teachers.
    - Sub-subseries I:B:3: Committees
      - NYSUT Committees, Pension Committee, Feb 1979 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Special Education, Feb 1979 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Higher Ed Council, Feb 1979 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Retirement Comm., Feb 1979 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Ed Affairs Comm., Mar 1979 (Item 5056)
      - Committee of 100, May 1979 (Item 3714)
      - NYSUT Committees, Educational Affairs, May 1979 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Task Force on Equitable School Funding, May 1979 (Item 5056)
      - Committee of 100 with Ray Skuse, Jun 1979 (Item 3714)
      - NYSUT Committees, Pension Committee, Jan 1980 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Special Ed Comm., Jan 1980 (Item 5056)
      - Committee of 100, Feb 1980 (Item 3714)
      - NYSUT Committees, Vocational Ed Committee, Feb 1980 (Item 5056)
      - Committee of 100, Mar 1980 (Item 3714)
      - NYSUT Committees, Pension Committee, Mar 1980 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Commission on Equitable Public School Funding, Mar 1980 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Task Force on Retired Teachers, Mel Aaronson, May 1980 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Various Committees, May 1980 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Labor Conference, May 1980 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Occupational Health Conf., Jan 1981 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Task Force on Academic Freedom planning RA workshop, Jan 1981 (Item 5308)
      - NYSUT Task Force on Labor Centennial meeting, Feb 1981 (Item 5378)
      - Committee of 100 meeting with Sanders, Hobart, before lobbying effort, Mar 1981 (Item 3714)
      - Committee of 100 Lobbying with Legislators, Mar 1981 (Item 3714)
      - NYSUT Nurses Advisory Committee 1st Meeting with NYSUT Staff, Apr 26, 1981 (Item 5402)
      - NYSUT Committees, Vocational Ed, May 1981 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Nurses Advisory Committee Meeting, John O'Leary and Staff, Aug 1981 (Item 5402)
      - NYSUT Committees, Meting about NYSUT Survey re: Part 200 regulations, Dec 1981 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Executive Comm. Meeting with Ambach [x], Jan 1982 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Committees, Commission On Equitable Public School Funding, Jan 1982 (Item 5056)
      - NYSUT Task Force on Educational Issues meeting, Feb 1982 (Item 5522)
      - Committee of 100 Lobbying in Albany, Mar 1982 (Item 3714)
      - Committee of 100, pre-lobbying session, May 1982 (Item 3714)
      - Committee of 100, Senator Linda Winikow of Spring Valley with Lower Hudson Dist., May 1982 (Item 3714)
      - Committee of 100, Tier III, Lobbying, undated (Item 3714)
      - Committee of 100, Sanders and Skuse, undated (Item 3714)
      - Committee on Educational Issues (NYSUT), undated (Item 4707)
      - NYSUT Committees - Scham, Norma; Daggett, Willard; Sanders, Dan; Garino, Robert, Dr., undated (Item 5056CR)
      - Special Services task force (NYSUT), undated (Item 5257)
      - [NYSUT?:] Academic Freedom and Task Force, undated (Item 5568)
    - Sub-subseries I:B:4: Locals and Teacher Associations
      - [NYSUT Local?] Abbot School TA, Arthur Jaffe President, Jun 20, 1976 (Item 4485)
      - Altmar Parish Williamstown TA [Includes but may not be limited to:] Cortese, Antonia; Tatko, Barbara; Farrell, Elsie; Maunder, Fran, Sep 1976 (Item 4630)
      - Amsterdam Teachers Strike, 1972 (Item 1682)
      - Amsterdam Teachers Association, Feb 1976 (Item 4145)
      - Amsterdam Teachers Talk about issues in Representation Vote, Jun 13, 1976 (Item 4465)
      - Amsterdam Teachers Association, Apr 1979 (Item 4145)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Arlington TA, Gadin Bodner Memorial Scholarship, 1979 (Item 5210)
      - Auburn TA, aid to Polish Relief Fund, undated (Item 3928)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Ausable Valley Central TA, undated (Item 5164)
      - Babylon TA, Frank Arena with Hobart, Ed Rogers, undated (Item 5197)
      - Bainbridge-Guilford TA, undated (Item 4750)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Baldwin Faculty Association, Oct 1973 (Item 2726)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Beekmantown TA, Feb 1980 (Item 5210)
      - Bellmore Faculty Organization, Dedication of Library, LI, undated (Item 2225)
      - Bellmore-Merrick Strike, Oct 1974 (Item 3354)
      - Bellmore-Merrick, Special Olympics, Jun 29, 1980 (Item 3354)
      - Bellmore-Merrick United Secondary Teachers, Jun 1981 (Item 3354)
      - Bellport Teachers Association, Yvonne Withers with James L. Vaughan and Reginald Washington, Oct 1975 (Item 3962)
      - Washington, Reginald, Bellport TA President, undated (Item 1208)
      - Berkshire Farms TA Negotiators, Mar 1981 (Item 5398)
      - Bethpage Congress of Teachers, newly elected officers, Oct 1972 (Item 2043)
      - Brentwood Teachers Association, Oct 1973 (Item 2710)
      - Zuckerman, Jack with Brentwood Teachers Association Scholarship Winners, undated (Item 4592)
      - Brewster TA Strike, Oct 1975 (Item 3968)
      - Briarcliff Teachers Association Conference, Jean Synal Speaking, May 1973 (Item 2526)
      - Briarcliff Teachers Association, Jan 1975 (Item 3513)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Broome BOCES TA, Easter Seals Kid Ryin Nugent, undated (Item 5196)
      - Buffalo Teachers Federation win gains in new contract, Contract Vote, 1972 (Item 2081)
      - Buffalo Teachers Federation, Jul 1975 (Item 3795)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Campbell TA Leaders, Coming TA leaders Johnson City Case, Dec 1975 (Item 4327)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Campbell TA, Jan 1976 (Item 4067)
      - Rathburn, Anita, Canastota TA, undated (Item 4958)
      - Obernesser, Jim, Cato-Meridian TA, undated (Item 4963)
      - Davis, Lee (Catskill TA President) with wife Pauline, Mar 1976 (Item 4189)
      - Glenn, Don, [NYSUT Local?] Cazenovia TA, undated (Item 4970)
      - Central Islip TA, Scholarship Funds, 1980 (Item 5271)
      - Jarvis, Darlene, Central Square TA, undated (Item 4969)
      - Wiesinger, Toni, Cheektowaga Central TA President, May 1975 (Item 3744)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Cheektowaga Central TA, Teachers and Community, Mar 1980 (Item 5210)
      - Freeman, Virginia, Clarkstown Teachers Association, Dec 1975 (Item 4334)
      - Gallo, Don, Clarkstown TA, May 1976 (Item 4297)
      - Clarkstown TA Humanism Conference, Edward Rauschart, 1978 (Item 4201)
      - Clarkstown TA, William Cea, 1980 (Item 4201)
      - Clarkstown TA, William Cea with Comm. Of Education, Ambach, strike, Sep 1980 (Item 4201)
      - Clarkstown TA, Special Olympics, 1982 (Item 4201)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Cobleskill TA President Hartman with Cortese on WGY annual Christmas Wish Campaign, Nov 1981 (Item 4639)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Cobleskill TA - Adams, William; Adams, Annemarie, undated (Item 4639CR)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Cobleskill United Teachers, Blair Hartman, Jean Stennett, Dan Sanders, Mar 1979 (Item 4639)
      - Farely, Mildred submits strike vote resolution [Cohoes TA], Oct 1973 (Item 2351)
      - Cohoes TA President Warren Mannix with Joe Loudis who was named outstanding educator of the year, Dec 1981 (Item 5066)
      - Mannix, Warren, Cohoes TA Press with Hobart and Ed Finkle, undated (Item 5066)
      - Rensselaer, Columbia-Greene BOCES, Support Service Staff Federation, Dec 1984 (Item 5726)
      - Teachers Association, Commack, Mid-Winter Gala, Feb 1973 (Item 2238)
      - Commack, LI, TA Charges Board Damages Districts' Education, May 1976 (Item 4240)
      - Commack, LI, Commack TA, 1979 (Item 4240)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Connetquot TA, Conference at Connetquot, Apr 1982 (Item 5210)
      - Long, Mary Ann, President of [NYSUT Local?] Cooperstown TA, Sep 1973 (Item 2261)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Cooperstown Teachers Association, Oct 1973 (Item 2619)
      - Levittown Teachers, Fund, Copiague TA, Mar 1979 (Item 3522)
      - Copiague TA, Honoring three members, Hotaling, Kulick and Levien, 1980 (Item 5259)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Rally, Corinth Teachers Association Members, undated (Item 4640)
      - Cornell Adjunct Faculty Federation, John Hudson [x], May 1981 (Item 5444)
      - Cornell University, Adjunct Faculty Federation Recognized as bargaining agent for LI, Westchester, etc., Feb 1981 (Item 340)
      - Corning Teachers Association, Sep 1975 (Item 3899)
      - Corning TA leaders review memorandum of agreement, Dec 1975 (Item 4058)
      - Corning Teachers Association, ratification of contract, Feb 1977 (Item 3899)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Dannemora Teachers Association negotiating team, first contract ever, Jan 1981 (Item 5349)
      - Depew Teachers Organization, Educator of the year Award to Dorothy Varley, Aug 1980 (Item 4928)
      - NYSUT Political Action, Depew TO, Nov 1980 (Item 4987)
      - Depew Teachers Organization, Political Action [Includes but may not be limited to:] Ventura, Anthony J., undated (Item 4928)
      - Deposit TA, undated (Item 4996)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Draper TA, undated (Item 2963)
      - Teachers and the Community, WGY Christmas Wish Campaign, [NYSUT Locals?] Duanesburg TA and Fort Plain District, Jan 1982 (Item 5509)
      - Dunkirk TA, gas well, Feb 1980 (Item 4863)
      - [NYSUT Local?] East Irondequoit teachers boost signs with District Director James Smith, Oct 1973 (Item 2722)
      - [NYSUT Local?] EITA [East Irondequoit Teachers Association] on Strike, support for EITA, Nov 1973 (Item 2760)
      - [NYSUT Local?] East Irondequoit, Marty Cullinan, 1979 (Item 2722)
      - East Islip TA, VOTE/COPE Campaign, Oct 1974 (Item 3355)
      - McCaffrey, Hugh E., wins higher pension benefits through East Meadow TA grievance, Feb 1976 (Item 3994)
      - East Meadow Teachers, strike, undated (Item 3264)
      - East Meadow Teachers, Check awarded to reading teachers, court case, undated (Item 3264)
      - East Ramapo United Teachers Association, undated (Item 4079)
      - Knapp, Rick, East Ramapo TA, undated (Item 4079)
      - Emhke, Cliff, East Syracuse-Minoa United Teachers, undated (Item 4956)
      - Eastchester TA, strike, Feb 1976 (Item 3971)
      - Eastchester TA, scholarship basketball game, undated (Item 4569)
      - Eastchester TA, David Kubaska, President, honors Jean Whitney Harold, past President, retiring, undated (Item 4621)
      - Eastchester TA Leaders Prison Bound, undated (Item 4621)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Ellenville, Ron Frantz, Feb 1980 (Item 5210)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Elmira Federation of Teachers, Apr 1974 (Item 2977)
      - Elmira Teachers Association, Annual Party, Gilbert Hendrix chats with members, Oct 1973 (Item 2735)
      - Elmira Teachers Association, Booth School, Jun 1979 (Item 2735)
      - Elmont Elementary Teacher Association workshop, undated (Item 2163)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Elmont Teachers, NYSUT fight for health coverage, May 1976 (Item 4410)
      - Shanker, Al speaking to members of [NYSUT Local?] Elwood Federation of Teachers, Jan 7, 1972 (Item 1572)
      - Endicott TA, teachers win back pay, Feb 1973 (Item 2177)
      - Endicott TA, Dane Helt, undated (Item 2177)
      - Faculty Association of Suffolk Community College, picket line, Ellen Schuler-Mauk, Tak Tow Chen, Jim DiSario, 1980 (Item 4707)
      - Fairport Educational Association, strike, undated (Item 3456)
      - Falconer Education Association has opened on East Main St. to bring Local's case for fair contract to public, May 1976 (Item 4417)
      - School For Deaf, [NYSUT Local?] Fanwood TA / Tara Denis, Apr 1979 (Item 1341)
      - Farmingdale Federation of Teachers, Jun 1974 (Item 3086)
      - Farmingdale Federation of Teachers, VOTE/COPE Campaign, Sep 1974 (Item 3298)
      - Farmingdale teachers association, strike, May 1976 (Item 3418)
      - Farmingdale, LI Teachers Strike, May 1976 (Item 4243)
      - Farmingdale teachers on strike, May 1976 (Item 4276)
      - Farmingdale teachers end strike, May 1976 (Item 4378)
      - Fayetteville-Manlius TA, undated (Item 4291)
      - Florida Teachers Association, Florida, NY, undated (Item 2145)
      - Franklinville TA, undated (Item 5174)
      - Freeport TA, Nov 1980 (Item 5317)
      - Freeport TA, Vincent Callaci and Dorothy Silverman, undated (Item 5317)
      - Parents As Reading Partners, Frontier Central TA, undated (Item 1062)
      - Spreter, Sue, Fulton TA, undated (Item 4967)
      - Fulton TA, undated (Item 5117)
      - Garden City TA, Levittown Fund, undated (Item 5016)
      - Garden City TA, undated (Item 5016)
      - Garden City TA, undated (Item 5032)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Gates Chili TA, Anthony LaMarca, Mar 1980 (Item 5210)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Thomas Sullivan (President of the Gates-Chili TA), scholarship recipients, 1981 (Item 5210)
      - Ryan, Patricia, West Genesee TA, undated (Item 4968)
      - Durkee, Dan, Teacher of the year, [NYSUT Local?] Genesee Valley TA, undated (Item 5354)
      - Geneva Teachers, Crisis Center, Nov 1975 (Item 3945)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Gilboa-Conesville, TA Leaders, May 1976 (Item 4278)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Gilboa-Conesville TA, Acid Rain, Jun 1980 (Item 4278)
      - Gloversville TA, guest speaker Al Shanker, Mar 1976 (Item 4187)
      - Gowanda Teachers Association Picket Board, Oct 1973 (Item 2731)
      - Gowanda Teachers Association, Conference Day, May 1981 (Item 2731)
      - Grand Island and Tonawanda Conference Days, Apr 1974 (Item 2945)
      - Grand Island TA members, with assistance from the local labor council, picket to protest board's foot-dragging in negotiations. George Wessel, president of the Buffalo AFL-CIO labor council, is shown along with the local's picket captain, Carol Gugino., undated (Item 5471)
      - Grand Island Teachers Association, Lynn Laman, "Citizen of the Year in Education", Feb 1982 (Item 5476)
      - Grand Island Teachers Association, Grand Island TA Day, 9/24, undated (Item 5476)
      - Great Neck TA, Special Olympics, Jan 1981 (Item 5356)
      - Great Neck TA, Mike Miyata, Feb 1981 (Item 5356)
      - Great Neck TA, Nurse-Teachers jobs restored, Apr 1981 (Item 5356)
      - Great Neck TA, Mary Bachand at RA, Apr 1981 (Item 5356)
      - Great Neck TA, Special Olympics, Jan 1982 (Item 5356)
      - Greenburgh Federation of Teachers, strike, Sep 1973 (Item 1843)
      - Greenburgh Federation of Teachers, Teaching Assistants, Mar 1980 (Item 1843)
      - Greenburgh Federation of Teachers, VOTE/COPE Campaign, undated (Item 1843)
      - Human Relations Conference, [NYSUT Local?] Greene TA, Nov 1981 (Item 2733)
      - Howell, Diana ([NYSUT Local?] Greene TA President), undated (Item 4183)
      - Springville Strike [Griffith Institute Faculty Association, NYSUT Local?], Sep 1975 (Item 3849)
      - Springville Strike [Griffith Institute Faculty Association, NYSUT Local?], Sep 1975 (Item 4361)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Guilderland TA, Canadian Festival, Feb 1980 (Item 5210)
      - [Half Hollow Hill TA] Teachers picket to stress, no contract, no work, Jun 1973 (Item 2662)
      - Half Hollow Hills TA, strike, Sep 1975 (Item 3868)
      - Roseman, Carol Half Hollow Hills President, Apr 1976 (Item 4118)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Hallen Teachers Association, Hallen School Special Ed, Mar 1980 (Item 5210)
      - Hamburg Teachers Association, Boston Valley School, Mar 1976 (Item 4157)
      - Hamburg Teachers Association, Apr 1976 (Item 4157)
      - Spreter, Bill, [NYSUT Local?] Hannibal TA, undated (Item 4965)
      - Harborfields Teachers UTH [United Teachers of Harborfields] with Millie Aebisher and Al Shanker, Jan 1978 (Item 4814)
      - Fuller, Paul, Harrison Association of Teachers receives check from NYSUT President Tom Hobart, Oct 1973 (Item 2708)
      - Harrison Strike, Sep 1973 (Item 1094)
      - Harrison Teachers Association, May 1974 (Item 3097)
      - Harrisville TA, undated (Item 4332)
      - Hartford TA, undated (Item 5208)
      - Hauppauge TA, Apr 1980 (Item 4880)
      - Hauppauge TA, Dollars for Scholars Drive, Oct 1980 (Item 4880)
      - Hauppauge TA, Parents and Teachers, undated (Item 4880)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Henderson TA, undated (Item 4716)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Heuvelton Teachers Association, contract agreement, Nov 1973 (Item 2789)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Heuvelton Teachers Association, President, Mar 1981 (Item 2789)
      - Hicksville, LI Federation of Teachers, Nov 1980 (Item 3148)
      - McPartin, Joe, Hicksville, LI Federation of Teachers, undated (Item 3148)
      - Edelman, Howard, [NYSUT Local?] Hicksville, LI Federation of Teachers, undated (Item 3148)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Hornell Teachers Association, undated (Item 3863)
      - Horseheads TA, Margaret Tagg, undated (Item 3293)
      - Horseheads Teachers Association Rally, undated (Item 3293)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Hudson Falls Non-Instructional EA, Christmas party for children, 1980 (Item 5329)
      - [NYSUT Local] Huntington, LI, undated (Item 4360)
      - Associated Teachers of Huntington, undated (Item 4360)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Irondequoit Teachers, undated (Item 3281)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Island Trees Reps., seminar on contract enforcement, Jun 1980 (Item 2330)
      - Carlson, Robert A. speaks at Jamestown Teachers Association, May 1974 (Item 3078)
      - Jamestown TA meeting [Includes but may not be limited to:] Hobart, Tom, Jun 1976 (Item 4552)
      - Jamestown TA Workshop, 1979 (Item 4552)
      - Jamestown, crisis HQ, undated (Item 2022)
      - Jamestown, NY, Strike, undated (Item 2073)
      - Jamestown TA - Jackson, Virgil; Wolfenden, Terry, undated (Item 4552CR)
      - Cashing, Betsy, Jamesville-Dewitt TA, undated (Item 4955)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Jeffersonville-Youngsville FA, undated (Item 5604)
      - Johnstown TA, Gary Kiev is congratulated by President Henry Diller due to reinstatement, Jan 1976 (Item 3992)
      - Johnstown TA, Rally during negotiations, Jan 1982 (Item 3992)
      - Johnstown TA visit NYSUT after reaffiliation, undated (Item 3992)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Keene Valley TA, contract settlement, Jun 1981 (Item 5449)
      - Benker, Donald, 81 E.D. 1 Director (Kenmore TA), Apr 1975 (Item 3685)
      - Kenmore TA, June Lynch, Jun 1980 (Item 4878)
      - Kenmore TA, John LaFalce, re: Title I at Kenmore TA School, May 1982 (Item 4878)
      - Kenmore TA - Planning Calendar Contest; Avery, Estelle, undated (Item 4878CR)
      - Kingston Federation of Teachers, Nov 1973 (Item 2749)
      - Kingston Federation of Teachers, Jun 1974 (Item 2749)
      - Kingston Federation of Teachers, Al Shanker Presents Award to Kingston Federation of Teachers Past President Don Sweeny (30th Anniversary), undated (Item 2749)
      - Lackawanna Teachers Federation, undated (Item 4746)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Lake Placid TA, undated (Item 4986)
      - Lakeland Federation of Teachers, strike, Sep 1977 (Item 4809)
      - Lakeland Federation of Teachers, Joseph Barni Thanks Steelworkers, Apr 1978 (Item 4809)
      - Lakeland Teachers, Strike, 42 Days, 1977-78, undated (Item 4809)
      - Lakeland Teachers - Blattman, Abel, undated (Item 4809CR)
      - Barni, Joseph, Lakeland TA President with Tom Hobart, undated (Item 4948)
      - Levittown Teachers, strike, Sep 1978 (Item 3522)
      - Cuomo, Mario with Levittown Teachers, Nov 1978 (Item 3522)
      - Levittown Teachers, NYSUT Levittown Comm. Meeting, Biltmore, Mar 1979 (Item 3522)
      - Levittown Teachers, St. John's Lutheran, Jun 1979 (Item 3522)
      - Culinan, Martin, Levittown Teachers, undated (Item 2590)
      - Levittown Teachers support dismissed teacher at Island Trees, undated (Item 3522)
      - Levittown Teachers, with Glen Cove TA President giving Cullinan Award, undated (Item 3522)
      - Levittown Teachers, Mary Grough Meets with UFT District 12, undated (Item 3522)
      - Levittown TA - Ardsley Congress of Teachers; Bonder, Annette; Wantagh, Long Island; East Meadow Teachers; Farmingdale Federation of Teachers; Carmody, Jane; Caubisens, Marietta; Cestaro, Tom; New Utrecht HS; McEneaney, Jerry; District 3 UFT; Penfield EA; Deedy, Kenneth; Clark, Ray; St. John's Hospital LI, Federation of Health Professionals; Smedly, David; Cortese, Antonia; Pappas, Tom; Ronald (President, Sayville TA); Cuomo, Mario, undated (Item 3522CR)
      - Lewiston Porter Education Association, Dinner, Feb 1977 (Item 2196)
      - Lewiston Porter Education Association, negotiating committee, undated (Item 2196)
      - Lewiston Porter UT, Richard R. Anderson, 1979 (Item 2196)
      - Lewiston Porter UT, Bonnie Northrop, President, undated (Item 2196)
      - Lewiston Porter Education Association, Rep. Council, undated (Item 2196)
      - Lewiston Porter UT, honors Price, Cole, and Oravec, undated (Item 2196)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Liberty Teachers Association, Aug 1975 (Item 3839)
      - Lindenhurst Teachers Association, Jul 1974 (Item 3150)
      - Lindenhurst United Teachers, training center, May 1976 (Item 4382)
      - Lindenhurst Teachers protest against cuts, May 1976 (Item 4412)
      - Lindenhurst Teachers Association, Kist receives check, arbitration success on longevity increments, 1980 (Item 3150)
      - United Liverpool Faculty Association [Includes but may not be limited to:] Zalewski, Steve, undated (Item 4959)
      - Liverpool FA, undated (Item 5022)
      - Locust Valley School EA, support suspended colleague, May 1981 (Item 5431)
      - Long Island University Brooklyn Center, Strike [Includes but may not be limited to:] Lubin, Alan; Margolis, Michael; Polishook, Irwin, Sep 1979 (Item 4762)
      - Long Island University Brooklyn Center, Rally, Picketing and Strike, Oct 1980 (Item 4762)
      - Long Island University, Brooklyn Center, Strike, Nov 1980 (Item 4762)
      - Long Island University, Brooklyn Center, Faculty Demonstration, undated (Item 4762)
      - Graham, Al (First Vice President), Mamaroneck Teachers Association, May 1976 (Item 4264)
      - Malone TA building Rep. Workshop, Jun 20, 1976 (Item 4477)
      - Mamaroneck TA Counseling Department, 1980 (Item 5270)
      - Mamaroneck TA with David Rockefeller, Jr., Won Art Grants, 1982 (Item 5270)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Marathon Teachers Association Meeting, undated (Item 2049)
      - Dross, Karen, [NYSUT Local?] Marathon TA, undated (Item 4070)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Marcellus TA Arbitration win, undated (Item 4368)
      - Marion TA Dinner, Mar 1981 (Item 5387)
      - Maryvale TA John P. Tammaro, Distinguished Science Teacher Award for 1981 (Item 5409)
      - Massapequa Federation of Teachers, Nov 1973 (Item 2755)
      - McPartlin, Joe (Massapequa FT President), Nov 1973 (Item 2756)
      - Teachers end negotiations successfully in Massapequa, undated (Item 1179)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Mexico TA, undated (Item 4960)
      - Middle Country TA Conference Day, Feb 1981 (Item 5358)
      - Middle Country TA Concert, Scholarship Awards, etc., May 1981 (Item 5358)
      - [NYSUT Local?] Middleburgh TA, Russian gymnast teaching students, undated (Item 5464)
      - Middletown Teachers Association Picket Newburgh Offices, Oct 1973 (Item 2711)
      - Girolamo, Joseph (President of the Miller Place, LI), Mar 1974 (Item 3139)
      - LI Locals, Tri-Teachers LI Association, Miller Place TA Strike, Sep 1979 (Item 5206)
      - Mineola TA Crisis Comm. [Includes but may not be limited to:] LaMontaine, Don; Levine, Norman; Smith, Jim; Merola, Vito, undated (Item 4608)
      - Mineola Teachers Association School Strike, undated (Item 4631)
      - Mohonasen TA 1980 Board Meeting (Item 4573)
      - Gruber, Gene, Moravia TA, undated (Item 4953)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Moriah CTA, Bargaining, Sep 1980 (Item 5210)
      - Miscellaneous Locals, Moriah CTA, NYSUT Stress Workshop, Nov 1980 (Item 5210)
      - Moriah CTA, Sandra Smith, Jan 1982 (Item 5293)
      - Mount Sinai TA, Kanter, Randee (President), Blood Drive, May 1981 (Item 5428)